Man, it's cold... Better hurry
home so I can have a drink.
Help me...
Please... help... Help me, please...
Who's there?! You okay?
SEARCHING FOR A FAMILIAR IS TOO DIFFICULT!!
"Searching for a Familiar
Is Too Difficult!!"
Hey, Doux! Where are you?
Papa, look!
Doux?! Did you save another
peculiar creature?
This is the Mr. Lizard I saved
from the river the other day!
He turned this big!
The other day...? You've been
taking care of it ever since?
Yup!
I've been feeding him every day,
bathing him, and sleeping with him.
Hm? Are you hungry?
Here, open wide!
Doux... the only ones you
should be taking care of
are demons or magical beasts.
Honestly, what are we going to do
about everything clinging to you?
No, Your Majesty.
Ah! Big Sister Jahi!
This actually works in our favor.
Look, look! Isn't he cute?
What do you mean, Jahi?
I will be conducting a trial in
making pacts today.
Pacts?
Magical beast pacts.
It's rather worrisome if Lady Doux were
to go outside the castle while we're away
since she lacks any sense of caution...
So we will have her form a pact
and have the magical beast that
is her familiar protect her.
Creatures quickly take
a liking to Lady Doux,
so she should be able to form a pact with
a magical beast without fighting it.
I see! The more ways to
protect her, the better!
Well done, Jahi!
Your praise honors me.
But I had also previously given
Doux a staff to help protect her.
It opened!
What just...
I wanna touch your head!
Th-That staff is a bit...
Hm... I guess that staff didn't work.
In that case, my latest creation
is the slaughter pendant!
Let us be on our way, Lady Doux!
Lady Doux, there are two ways to form
a pact with a magical beast.
Give them some of your blood, and if they
accept it, that creates a blood pact.
The other method is to create a pact
using magic, called a magic pact.
Magical beasts are beasts
that possess magic.
Form a pact, and the magical beast will
use that magic to fight alongside you
and sometimes become your shield.
They are your loyal minions.
Huh?
Which means... no matter what happens,
the one you form a pact with
will always be by your side.
Then Doux wants to form a
pact with Mr. Lizard!
I don't sense any magic from that lizard.
It is impossible to form a
pact with a normal lizard.
Okay...
First, let us find a magical beast.
Is that a magical beast?
It is not.
How about that?
What about...
It is not!
Hm... We sure aren't finding
any magical beasts.
The animals love her... Perhaps this
is a "pact" in its own way...
Hm?
Help me...
Huh?
Please... help. Help... me...
Ah! Lady Doux!
H-Help me...
Please... I beg of you...
It talked!
What is a Salamandra doing here?
Please step back, Lady Doux!
Ouchie, ouchie, go away!
Lady Doux!
Don't use your magic on
such frivolous things!
Did the ouchie go away?
Th-Thank you very much...
You can't go around saving everything
as if it's the same as breathing!
Please be my familiar.
A Salamandra isn't a magical beast!
Not to mention, the way you're trying to
form a pact is totally wrong, too!
Is it?
Run!
What brought that on sudde...
Who are you?
Hunting... failed...
Because you yelled...
You yelled "Run"... You betrayed us...
Because... Salamandra betray us...
Ah!
Yes... Obey, Salamandra...
There won't be a next time...
Yes...
The Salamandra...
A proud and noble dragon
that controls fire...
is being controlled by these small fry?
Small fry...?
No...
Swords, bludgeoning, fire, and ice
all have no effect on us...
We are pishachas...
We are demons that lurk in the shadows...
Pishachas? I've never
heard that name before.
Are they demons from another world?
We don't need this useless
dragon anymore...
It is now merely flesh
that we will consume...
Are you also delicious flesh?
This isn't good... Lady Doux!
Huh? I tried to fix them and they melted.
We feel so refreshed!
So they're weak against healing magic.
Lady Doux, make the
others feel better, too.
Okay!
No!
W-Wait! Wait!
Ouchie, ouchie, go away!
No!
The ouchie went away!
Refreshed!
I-Impossible! She's just a little brat...
Curse you... In that case...
What?!
Wow! So big!
Lady Doux!
Ouchie, ouchie, go away!
Die!
I-Impossible! Pishachas are immortal!
Wow!
Refreshed!
I'm terribly sorry.
I know I was being controlled,
but what I did was awful...
I must repay you with my life.
Before that, I need to ask you...
You were working with them,
so why did you yell, "Run"?
That's because...
atop her head...
That dragon is my child.
What?!
Hm?
Join us!
I refuse!
When the pishachas captured me,
I risked my life to
let my little one escape.
Because you took my child
in and fought valiantly,
I learned that my child was still alive.
I cannot repay this great debt
by becoming your familiar,
but I give my life to you.
So please boil me or
cook me as you'd like.
Just please, spare my child...
If you can't be my familiar,
then let's be family!
If we're family, we'll all
be able to stay together!
Right? Big Sister Jahi?
No, not "Right?"!
Though, I mean, she would
prove to be a powerful ally...
I, Salamandra, swear to
protect you with my life.
Big Sister Jahi...
Even if I allow this, there's no
guarantee that the demon king will.
That's amazing, Doux!
I never thought you would manage
to recruit a Salamandra!
This Mr. Lizard was her baby!
Is that so? I guess all
your care paid off.
My child is so brilliant!
All right! We'll throw a sweet
potato party to celebrate
since Doux loves them so much!
Okay, Papa!
THE PAIRIKA IS TOO SEXY!!
"The Pairika Is Too Sexy!!"
The torture isn't working?
Yes. We captured a rather
suspicious man outside the castle.
We were trying to get him to
tell us what he was plotting...
But none of our torture
methods have been successful.
So you're trying to come
up with another method?
Yes. I was hoping to get
your thoughts on this...
Wah!
Wh-What are you... d-doing?!
Wh-Who are you?!
What are you...?!
L-Lady Doux?!
Master!
Well done, Doux! That was impressive.
The "Draw on Her Face with
Lipstick" plan was a success!
Thaiti?!
That makeup looks great on you, Jahi.
Yeah! It looks great!
Who is that? Do you know her?
Yes... Well, we trained together,
and I can't seem to be rid of her.
After training, I was assigned
to the combat unit
while Thaiti was assigned to the
seduction witches, the Pairika.
The Pairika are a special unit
comprised of female demons who
specialize in seducing men...
But she's been stuck as
an apprentice forever
Yay!
because all she ever does is pull pranks.
I see...
What are you even doing with
Lady Doux in the first place?!
What?
It's because this little
one became my apprentice!
Okay.
That should do it.
Wow!
Wait, aren't you the demon king's...
Lady, this is funny!
You've got some potential, kid.
Big Sister Thaiti is Doux's
pranks teacher!
Heh!
The last title a forever apprentice
like yourself deserves is "master."
Oh? Are you really one to talk?
Doux told me all about it...
You're giving Doux here
trials to become a proper demon, but...
Sounds like you're having some trouble.
That's why I'm here to
give you some suggestions!
A trial of seduction that'll
work better than torture!
What?
Seduction?
Ooh, I wanna try that! Doux
wants to try seduction!
What? Don't tell me you taught
anything like that to Lady Doux...
Oh, I'm so proud of you, my daughter!
You're so enthusiastic about these trials!
So...
What's seduction mean?
That's the man I mentioned earlier.
No torture seems to work on him.
He is quite the villain,
so do be careful, Lady Doux.
Okay!
If you let me handle it,
it'll be easy as pie.
What are you doing here?
I'm fairly certain I asked for an actual
Pairika who can show her how it's done.
Well, I'm the most knowledgeable
about this trial.
I'm a professional, after all!
Professional prankster, yes.
You don't even know how to torture
people properly, so keep quiet.
I have every method of
seduction stored in my head!
Demonstrating any of them is easy.
Just you watch, Doux.
Okay!
Whatever you say, forever apprentice.
You and those giant udders that're
wasted on you can shut up!
I'll show you how it's really
done, so keep your mouth shut!
You two must be really close!
How...?
Hey, mister...
Aren't you tired of being trapped here?
Stop holding onto those secrets...
Let it all out...
Then you can have some fun with me...
And feel much better.
Th-That was perfect!
There's no way anyone
wouldn't fall for that!
I did that perfectly, just
like the manual said!
How do you like that, Jahi?!
Now I can be just like my sisters and...
Hey.
Huh?
You're gonna piss your mom off
being precocious like that.
A little brat like you should go back
home and suck on your mommy's teats.
I'll murder you!
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't kill him before
he tells us his secrets!
But he was mean and mocking me!
Do you know how hard I've worked
to get men to fall for me?!
J-Just stop.
I can't handle any
more secondhand embarrassment.
Embarrassment?!
Well then why don't you try it?!
You're just all talk anyway!
Someone please stop this idiot.
All of you are so mean to me!
I figured this would happen.
Very well.
Are you next? No matter what you try—
I hear that men have a
weakness for bosoms.
How about you?
N-Not interested...
Or how about...
This?
Very well.
Then I'll just... make you forget...
all about your little secrets by...
I...
I can't... do this!
It's indecent!
Indecent, I tell you!
Why must I offer my body to someone
I'm not even interested in?!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
You're the one who—
Is that seduction, too?
No, that's just violence.
Master?
I'm sorry, Doux.
I... just wanted to get back at everyone.
I have a body of a child, and everyone
around me treats me like one.
I know very well that I'm
not suited for seduction...
But I don't have any other talents...
So no matter where I go... I'm just
going to get left behind again.
That's why I thought that if
I was able to do this trial,
everyone would finally accept me.
And my selfishness just
ended up ruining your trial.
But you didn't ruin it.
I did ruin it! There's nothing
I can teach you, Doux!
But you did teach me.
But I haven't done anything...
But you did teach me, Master!
That's my...
Just watch!
Huh? Wait, Doux!
Lady Doux?
Hey, what're you gonna try now?
Let's have a staring contest...
Huh?
If you laugh you're gonna lose...
W-Wait, what are you...
This is Doux's serious face.
H-Hey... just what are you
trying to do, you little brat?
Tickle, tickle, tickle...
S-Stop! Stop that!
Doux wins!
Y-You didn't win anything!
Tickling someone is playing dirty!
Also, if the one who laughs
first loses, then you...
This is Doux's serious face.
Those scribbles... Now I get it!
How stupid! Like I'd tell you my secrets
even if I lost at this nonsense!
Tickle, tickle, tickle...
That was a lie! I was just kidding!
I'll talk! I'll talk, so please!
I'm the one who painted
on the castle walls!
I'm so sorry!
So... please, just stop tickling me!
Impossible...
Torture and seduction didn't
work at all, yet this...
childish prank got to him?
Wait! It was so much trouble
to get that off the walls!
So you were the one responsible?!
Doux...
This was all according to plan!
A trial like this is nothing
when Doux and I work together!
Now, hold on!
This was supposed to be
a trial of seduction.
Not to mention, Lady Doux was
the one who made him confess!
You didn't do anything.
Nope.
I was able to do this because
Master taught me how to do pranks.
Big Sister Thaiti is my
pranks master.
That was a huge success, Doux!
Yup!
Yay!
Okay! Now, let's start
the trial of pranks!
"PRANK TIME"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: YURI MORITA
SONG: DOUX & THAITI
Okay, Master!
Huh?
Jan, jan, jan, jan
Jan, jan, jan, jajan
Pranks are so fun
It's so fun to laugh and smile
It's okay to go overboard
Just don't get yelled at
Let's have a staring contest
If you laugh, you're gonna lose
Wahahahahahahahaha haha
Jan, jan, jan, jan
Jan, jan, jan, jajan
Let's have a staring contest
If you laugh, you're gonna lose
Wahahahahahahahaha haha
That's enough already!